Re-Animated is a comedy, family, animation film directed by Bruce Hurwit.
Jimmy is the kid everybody ignores and uses.
One day, he gets into a freak accident.
The only way for him to survive is a brain transplant.
He gets the brain of Milt Appleday, a famous cartoon creator.
And when he wakes up, he can see cartoons!
Jimmy Roberts, played by Dominic Janes.
Jimmy's Dad, played by Bil Dwyer.
Captain Roberts, played by Rachel Quaintance.
Nurse, played by Jennifer De Minco.
Head of Appleday Board, played by Neil Flynn.
Scott / Dancer, played by Tucker Barkley.
Re-Animated is a 2006 American live-action animated teen fantasy-comedy
television film that aired on Cartoon Network on December 8, 2006.
It was the first original production on the genre for the network.
It was released on DVD on September 11, 2007, and serves as a pilot for the follow-up
series Out of Jimmy's Head, which premiered on September 14, 2007.
It received negative reviews from critics upon release.
The film's animation was produced by Renegade Animation, which
previously produced Hi Hi Puffy AmiYumi for Cartoon Network.
The film explores themes of alien, theme park, brain transplant.
The tone is lighthearted.